How long are you gonna take eating, huh?
You're an eyesore.
Damn evil-looking brat.
I'm sorry.
I can't hear you!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
...you. I'll...
Hey, stop!
Oyamada-kun, give that back.
"It's this year's greatest
super-romance novel!" Well, dang!
So you're one of those sweets-for-brains
who read romance novels, Ayaka-tan?
I-Is that a problem?
Bah! Is this for real?
Where's the line breaks?
This wondrous mountain view helps expand our
imagination of things outside our daily life.
You should take a good
look at it as well, Itsuki.
I know, Sis.
Ah, what should I do?
We were on the bus
for a school field trip.
Oyamada was excited and
teasing our class president.
Our other classmates kept their heads
down while the "elites" laughed away.
The only ones acting normal were the
Takao sisters and our apathetic teacher.
If I made a noble attempt to intervene,
I'd probably look pretty cool.
But having "air" like me step in would amount
to little more than a gentle breeze.
Total effect: zero. Nothing.
Insubstantial. Fruitless.
Oyamada-kun, cut it out already!
Like I said, I'll give it back
if you gimme your R@IN info.
Hey, Oyamada. Just give it back to her.
Huh?
Mimori Touka-kun, huh? Um, so...
What is it, huh?
What's gotten into you?
I mean, look at her.
Sogou-san seems genuinely upset over it.
- So...
- Huh?
S-S-S-So cool! Way too cool!
Huh? Hmm? Seriously, what is this?
An "air-man" finally staging a revolt?
Mimori-kun?
Give it back to her, Shougo.
Forget that, Takuto. Let's kill time by teasin'
Mimori-senpai who thinks he's hot stuff now!
No, I don't plan on doing that.
I haven't the slightest interest in Mimori.
That's super cold, Takuto.
Dang, man! I'm not icy enough for that.
Guess that's the difference
between you and me.
I can ignore whatever you do to Mimori,
but give Sogou back her book.
This little song and dance is repulsive.
That's our Kirihara-kun.
That should put an end to it, right?
My bad, Sogou. I got a little carried away.
Forgive and forget, yeah?
Hey, Yasu!
Mimori-senpai's usually air, and even he
went above and beyond to trigger an event,
so why are you, the bottom of the
2-C cast, acting like nothing's happening?
That's cold, you know!
That's enough now. It won't help anyone
if you drive him to suicide.
Yasu, if you're gonna do it,
do it when I'm not your teacher.
Okay, I'll hold back.
He's right. That wasn't like me.
For me to do something like that...
It must've been because of that dream.
Thanks to Mimori-senpai, the backdrop
to my fun field trip has turned real frosty.
- Thanks to Mimori-senpai, the backdrop
- Pierce the myriad borders to those unknown to me,
to my fun field trip has turned real frosty.
- and summon those brave of heart and spirit.
- People are totally raining on my parade this time.
- Under the guidance of Goddess Vicius's light,
manifest here in Alion.
Under the guidance of Goddess Vicius's light,
- Huh? Where are we?
- Under the guidance of Goddess Vicius's light,
manifest here in Alion.
- Huh? Where are we?
- Is this a dream?
Some kind of prank?
What is all this?
You are our only hope
of striking down evil.
Welcome, heroes from another world.
I am the goddess, Vicius. I welcome you all.
THE GODDESS ANNOUNCING HER SUMMONS
- Here in Alion, whenever the vast evil
known as the Great Demon Empire appears,
we summon heroes from another world.
Roughly 200 years ago, the efforts of
the heroes saw this grand evil defeated,
but after a long time, the Great
Demon Empire has resurfaced once more.
You are the chosen heroes.
So please, will you lend us
your power once more?
So we're in another world?
- Seems so?
- Idiot. It's just a dream.
I don't understand any of this.
Wait, we were on the bus, yeah? Have we died?
It must be some prank, right? Though
I'm not getting any signal on my phone.
Where's our luggage? I can't do my makeup.
Everyone, calm down. Your teacher's here, too.
I don't know what's going on
right now, either.
So for now, let's listen to
this goddess's explanation.
Thank you very much, Mr. Teacher.
A spacious room built out of stone.
Ancient-style fire baskets.
Soldiers wielding swords and spears.
And a goddess with golden eyes.
Is this really some other world, then?
Basically, you want us to defeat this
Great Demon Empire or whatever it's called?
That is the case, yes.
And if we don't help you?
Then you'll never be able
to return to your world.
Is there a way to return?
The reverse summoning ritual requires
a special element known as demon king essence.
Currently, there are only two
known methods for obtaining it.
One is to obtain the heart of the demon king,
the source of demon king essence.
The other is to collect the demon king essence
released upon the defeat of the demon king
in the crystal on this necklace.
That's all very convenient for you!
No, screw you! This "Great Demon Empire"
has nothing to do with us!
Would you please save our world,
O heroes of salvation?
U-Um, may I ask a few questions?
Go ahead.
I-I'm Sogou Ayaka.
You are well-mannered, Miss Sogou.
What is your question?
A-As you can see,
we're all just ordinary humans.
You want us to be your "heroes of salvation,"
but I can't see how we have the power to help.
Don't worry.
You all possess powers
that other humans do not.
- B-But we've had no indication of that.
- Why does something feel off?
- Yes, I'm sure you didn't.
Not before you were summoned here. Bring it.
Yes, ma'am.
Another world? Hah.
This is just some prank, right?
I'm gettin' sick of all these lame jokes.
That goddess...
Is something happening?
Huh? What's this?
What?
I'm kind of scared.
What is that?
A monster?
O holy flame that drives away evil.
In the name of the goddess, Vicius,
I command you to burn this evil to cinders.
Fireball.
Minamino-san!
I see. Viewing this world as different from
our own, possibly even as a different planet,
seems the optimal choice at present.
Come, heroes. It is time to reveal
the skills hidden within you.
Please come this way, one at a time.
You have talent.
Oh? Light this great means...
Now, this is wonderful!
I don't really get it,
but I got great results! So hot!
This world ain't so bad!
A hot wind's blowin' my way!
He's so full of himself.
Oh! I-Impossible!
Th-The Appraisal Crystal shattered!
Was that something amazing just now?
How wonderful, Sir Kirihara.
You're the ultimate rank: S-Class!
Whoa!
You use our alphabet in your world?
The translator optimizes it
for your ease of understanding.
Then, what does the "S" mean?
The "S" stands for "Special."
So what class am I? I'm hot stuff, right?
You're A-Class, Sir Oyamada.
Tsk. Guess there's no beating Takuto.
What in the world?
Oh, my! You're also S-Class, Miss Sogou!
Another A-Class!
What's this?
A third S-Class?
We're lucky to get even one
in a single summoning.
These are the best summoning
results we've ever had!
Now, next up, it's...
M-Mimori Touka.
Go ahead, Sir Mimori.
Purple?
Also, isn't my light the
weakest of everyone's so far?
Okay, next, please.
Next, please.
U-Um, what class am I?
Next!
She's ignoring me.
She's pretending I don't exist.
Like I'm a background character. I guess
even in another world, I get treated like air?
Well, that's reality for you. I can't become
anyone special, even in this other world.
Yeah, that's just Mimori Touka.
I'm fine with that.
We've seen this reaction in the past.
It's the same as that of the dark hero,
reputed to be the strongest of all.
We have a bountiful crop this time.
I knew it.
I knew my time was coming.
Okay, everyone, have you memorized
how to confirm your stats?
Stats: Open.
Looking at it now,
these numbers seem unusually low.
The Status Adjustment Value
represents the numerical value of the boost
to your physical abilities.
The screen is designed in a way
that should be familiar to you as well.
As a goddess, I can do these things for you.
Unique Skill: Inflict Status Ailments?
Unique skills are special skills
that only that individual can use.
Some of you may already
possess innate ones,
but there are others you can awaken later,
so please don't worry too much.
That's enough explanations now, goddess.
Hey, Oyamada. Watch how
you talk to the goddess.
You're just a D-Class hero. You think
you can talk to an A-Class hero like that?
You're always so condescending to us,
Teach, but you stand below us now.
Must be giving you chills.
Now, we have one more
important ritual to conduct.
Sir Touka Mimori, please come this way.
Huh? Who, me?
- Did I do something?
- Just shut up and go.
Touka Mimori, you are E-Class,
the lowest rank of all the heroes here.
In the past, the lowest-ranked heroes
have always dragged down the stronger ones.
So after a certain point, it was decided
we would start dealing with such heroes.
"Dealing" with?
Yes, dealing with them.
However, suddenly dealing with them on the
spot often comes as a shock to other heroes,
even causing them
to fight amongst themselves.
So it was decided we would grant
even the lowest-ranked hero a chance.
What do you mean by that?
That teleportation circle transports
the lowest-ranked hero to a set of ruins.
If they survive the ruins and reach
the surface, we interfere no more.
Alion grants that person
the right to live freely.
Are these ruins dangerous?
Who can say? We've sent many criminals
deemed highly dangerous
and a great number of heroes
to these ruins in the past.
Well, I suppose I'll make an exception
and tell you the name of the ruins.
They are known as...
the Ruins of Disposal.
Disposal?
What does that mean?
Wait! Goddess!
I have a unique skill!
What about it?
Mine is the skill: "Inflict Status Ailment"!
It allows me to inflict
paralysis, poison, and—
Listen up.
In this world, status ailment spells
and skills are generally worthless.
All of them have too low a success rate.
Even when they succeed,
they barely affect low-ranked monsters,
let alone middle-ranked ones,
and their duration is far too short.
N-No way!
In short, your skill is trash-tier.
Trash-tier?
Worse yet, it's probably
because you're E-Class,
but your stats are also too low.
Even if you level up, you shouldn't
expect much growth in those values.
Are we done here?
But you're the one who summoned me and
made me a hero. Now you're disposing of me?
- That's just completely—
- Now you're just being disgraceful.
Now you're just being disgraceful. Hurry up and finish this.
- The girls are all tired.
Don't you feel bad for them?
- Read the room, Mimori!
- Kirihara-kun's so kind!
- He's the air in the room, so he can't.
- That's our S-Class!
- Nice one.
- Hurry it up!
Are you okay, Mimori?
Y-Yasu?
Huh?
What do you think you're saying?
Huh? What?
It's Yasu-"san," right?
You're the lowest-ranked E-Class, so you need
to show more respect to an A-Class like me.
Well, do your best to live with what
little time you have left, Mr. Trash Hero.
Now, let's begin the ritual.
When you're summoned,
every hero is granted a unique item.
That pathetic-looking
leather bag is your unique item.
When you pour magic into the gem, it'll glow.
- Though all it does is glow.
- Please wait! This is all wrong!
Please wait! This is all wrong!
Mimori-kun is our classmate, isn't he?
The S-Class...
This is unforgivable!
We should release him right away—
Sogou?
Now, everyone. Please burn the sight
of this Trash Hero onto your eyelids.
This is the end that awaits the have-nots.
Or, to put in your world's terms, the losers.
However, you are all winners.
Only a tragic fate awaits losers.
You asshole.
Oh?
Paralyze!
How insolent. That was never
going to work on a goddess.
I have a Dispel Bubble
protective barrier active constantly.
It automatically provides total
defense against status ailment spells.
Everyone, this is your E-Class loser.
Your trash hero.
Draconic Buster.
Looks like I can use mine.
I was just giving it a quick test run.
Sorry about that.
Please be more careful in the future.
Now then.
Later, Bottom Hero.
Mimori Touka. R.I.P.
Air shouldn't be wasting my precious time.
If you're going to disappear,
hurry up and do it.
- If you're going to disappear,
- Damn it all.
Damn it all.
They're all scum.
Do you have any last words?
Why are you crying?
You understand, don't you?
No matter how much you repress it
and pretend to be a harmless person,
that's nothing like your true self.
- that's nothing like your true self.
- Enough. It doesn't matter.
Enough. It doesn't matter.
You're frustrated.
Show them your true colors.
Show them the true self
you've been suppressing this whole time.
Go to hell, you lousy goddess.
If I make it back alive,
you'd better be ready for me.
Stats: Open.
Unable to open because
your vision is obscured.
Oh, there it is.
I just pour magic into this, right?
Like this?
It really does feel like I'm using magic.
This feels more like a cave
than a set of ruins.
A broken skull? It was split in two?
What did that?
That's obvious. Something in these ruins.
Our levels, our essence, and our hostility
are just too different! I'm shivering!
So th-this is genuine hostility?
This is just giving me away!
Follow your instincts and run!
I don't want to die!
I'm crying again.
I'm not happy or sad.
I'm just scared!
Huh?
No, that's not it. I'm not scared.
It's an emotion I only felt recently.
That's right. I'm not scared. Damn it all.
I'm frustrated.
This is how Mimori Touka meets his end.
I have no weapons.
My stats are trash. My skill is major trash.
Checkmate.
Out of options.
- Hurry up and finish this.
- Read the room, Mimori.
- He's the air in the room, so he can't.
I want power.
Paralyze!
Huh?
It actually worked?
But that goddess said status ailments
rarely worked, even on low-ranked monsters.
Is a minotaur a low-ranked one?
No, it's not. Then, was it a miracle?
Did I just get lucky with it?
That must be it.
I can feel it.
Genuine, unadulterated,
unfiltered hostility.
Is it killing to eat? To survive?
I don't know.
Either way, it's hostility.
A bird monster?
Like a cockatrice or something?
No way.
I don't want to die!
I don't want to die! I don't want to die!
Paralyze.
It worked? So it wasn't a miracle?
What if my skill working a second time
wasn't a miracle, but inevitable?
What if my status ailment skill
is something completely different
from similar magic in this world?
Stats: Open.
I don't have any MP left.
I used this skill once each on the
goddess, the minotaur, and this thing.
I also charged my leather bag twice.
So all that's left is my own MP
outside of the stats adjustments.
If that's not enough
for me to use my skill...
then I'm done for.
Poison.
I used it!
And I can stack it with Paralyze...
If my success rate is incredibly high,
regardless of the monster's rank...
and if the duration is incredibly long...
If that's true, then...
What?
You were trying to kill me, too, you know.
Is this because I used my own MP?
What'll happen if I keep using
my status ailment skill like this?
The minotaur!
Guess the effect of that
first Paralyze ran out.
You're trying to kill me, too, aren't you?
Can't fault the attempt.
But wouldn't the normal cliché be
for someone to come to my rescue now?
I hope you at least earn yourself
a grisly death, Touka Mimori!
Screw you!
I'll kill you.
I'm not a hero or a heroine.
I'm a background character.
No one's coming to my rescue.
So I'll kill to survive!
Don't rely on others. Don't count on
or expect anything from others.
I'll conquer it all!
Now, let's begin...
...my fight for survival!
THE RUINS OF DISPOSAL